唔
Hmmm
问题看上去无解啊
The problem appears to be unsolvable.
我们可以用电脑模拟计算
Maybe we could run some computer simulations.
变量太多  运行时间会很长
There are too many variables. It would take forever.
我们肯定漏掉了什么
We've got to be missing something.
重来一遍
Let's start again.
电影这里是七点二十上映  这里是七点四十
The movie is playing here at 7:20, here at 7:40,
这里是八点十分  这里八点四十五
here at 8:10 and here at 8:45.
这几个电影院得排除在外
These theaters have to be eliminated.
为什么  那里有最先进的数码影像技术
Why? They're state-of-the-art digital projection,
20道环绕立体声
20-channel surround sound.
没错  可是那里没有刨冰机
Yes, but they have no Icee machines.
还完全不理睬我那么多封投诉信 错上加错
Despite my aggressive letter-writing campaign, i might add.
这个影城怎么样 座椅舒适极了
What about the multiplex here? The seats are terrific.
它们只有Twizzlers没有Red Vines  [糖果品牌]
They have Twizzlers instead of Red Vines.
无论多好的腰椎支撑都是无法弥补的
No amount of lumbar support can compensate for that.
至少要一个小时吃饭
Well, it's gonna take at least an hour to eat,
在谢尔顿认证的电影院周边
xyzzz xyzzz and I don't see a Sheldon-approved restaurant
根本没有谢尔顿认证的餐厅
proximate to a Sheldon-approved theater.
我们可以看完电影再吃晚饭
We could eat after the movie.
不予通过
Unacceptable.
吃饭太晚会造成
The delay would result
明天早晨的大肠蠕动出现在工作时间
in tomorrow morning's bowel movement occurring at work.
等下  这里有个7-11便利店
Hang on, hang on. There's a 7-Eleven here.
我们可以偷偷把Slurpees[7-11出的冷饮]带进去  就当刨冰了
We smuggle Slurpies, which are essentially Icees,
藏大衣底下就行了
in under our coats,
这样我们就可以从容地先在这里  这里  或者这里吃饭了
after having a pleasant meal either here, here or here.
咱们刚才怎么就没想到呢
Wow. I don't see how we missed that.
不好意思  Slurpees哪里算得上刨冰呢
Excuse me, in what universe are Slurpies Icees?
所以我们刚才没想到
That's how we missed it.
谢尔顿  在此紧要关头  虽说没有先例吧
Sheldon, would you be prepared, on a non-precedential basis,
您能不能临时认同一下Slurpees等于刨冰
to create an emergency ad hoc Slurpie-Icee equivalency?
莱纳德  你明白我做不到的
Oh, Leonard, you know I can't do that.
好吧  我看我们只有一个选择了
Okay, I guess we only have one option.
是啊  别无它法
Yep, I don't see any way around it.
-再见  谢尔顿  -拜拜了 -好好看家
-Bye, Sheldon. -See ya. -Stay loose.
他们没有错  这是唯一的选择
They're right, it was the only option.
快关门  快关门
Ooh, ooh, shut the door, shut the door.
-咋了  -关就是了
- Why? - Just do it!
先进来再关门
Get inside and shut the door
你又没有说清楚
Well, you didn't specify.
莱纳德在么
Is Leonard around?
他去看电影了不带我
He went to the movies without me.
这是唯一的选择
It was the only option.
不好意思  我不知道这是哪种社交情况啊
I'm sorry, I don't understand which social situation this is.
您能给我点指引么
Could you give me some guidance as to how to proceed?
楼管就在楼下呢
The building manager's showing an apartment downstairs,
我还没有缴房租
and I haven't paid my rent.
明白了
Oh, I see.
佩妮  让我藏匿洛城房产商的逃犯
Penny, I'm not sure I'm comfortable harboring a fugitive
我有点怕怕
from the 2311 North Los Robles Corporation.
没什么大不了的  就是欠了点房租而已
It's no big deal. I'm just a little behind on my bills
因为餐厅缩减了我的工作时间
because they cut back my hours at the restaurant
我的车又坏了
and my car broke down.
你还记得么  几个月以前 我告诉过你引擎检修灯在闪
If you recall, I pointed out the "check engine" light to you several months ago.
引擎检修灯还好着呢 现在还闪呢
The "check engine" light is fine. It's still blinking away.
是那个可恶的引擎罢工了
It's the stupid engine that stopped working.
修车花了我将近 一千二百刀
It cost me like $1,200 to fix it.
依我看  你的所有问题
You know, it occurs to me you could solve all your problems
都可以通过多挣点钱来解决
by obtaining more money.
是啊  我看也是
Yes, it occurs to me, too.
等我一下
Hang on a moment.
来吧  拿一些
Here. Take some.
等你有钱了再还我
Pay me back when you can.
你这儿有很多钱啊
Wow, you got a lot of money in there.
所以我才派蛇守卫
That's why it's guarded by snakes.
拿一些吧
Take some.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
我从来都不傻
I'm never silly.
拿着
Here.
我不能要
No, I can't.
你不是需要钱么
Don't you need money?
-是啊  可是  -我用不到这些钱
- Well, yeah, but... - This is money I'm not using.
你要用钱怎么办
But what if you need it?
我的日常开支占我税后收入的46.9%
My expenses account for 46.9% of my after-tax income.
其余的部分分别藏在银行帐户里
The rest is divvied up between a small savings account,
这个隐蔽的花生糖的罐子里
this deceptive container of peanut brittle
还有超级英雄人偶的空心屁屁里
and the hollowed-out buttocks of a superhero action figure
他不得已才隐姓埋名得以终日
who shall remain nameless for his own protection.
或者是女她
Or her own protection.
拿一些吧
Take some.
真的么  你肯定么
Really? I mean, are you sure?
我最近没有什么大的开销
I see no large upcoming expenditures
除非他们发明了新的科技
unless they develop an affordable technology
能将我的骨骼铸成金刚狼一样的合金
to fuse my skeleton with adamantium like Wolverine.
他们在研究这个么
Are they working on that?
我衷心希望
I sincerely hope so.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
不行  谢尔顿  亲爱的
Oh, no, I can't. Sheldon honey,
我不希望你我之间 变得怪怪的
I don't want things to be weird between us.
如果我每天早晨上班之前 都要和你问早安
Won't it also be weird if I have to say hello to you every morning on my way to work
可是你却住在冰箱盒子里 用雨水洗头  不是也很奇怪么
and you're living in a refrigerator box and washing your hair with rain water?
等我有钱了就还你
I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
那是肯定的
Of course you will.
没钱你也还不了
It's impossible to pay me back sooner than you can.
我假设你遵循前因后果
Assuming you subscribe
与时间的线性关系
to a linear understanding of time and causality.
我已经开始后悔了
I'm regretting this already.
我反复考虑过了
You know, I've given the matter some thought,
我宁可自己是一只家养宠物
and I think I'd be willing to be a house pet
也不愿意成为高智能的外星人
to a race of super-intelligent aliens.
有意思
Interesting.
问我为什么
Ask me why.
一定要问么
Do I have to?
当然
Of course.
这样对话才能进展下去
That's how you move a conversation forward.
为什么呢
Why?
这样学习的机会 会比较充裕
The learning opportunities would be abundant.
并且  我喜欢被人抓抓肚皮
Additionally, I like having my belly scratched.
佩妮  上班还好么
Hey, Penny. How was work?
妙极了
Great.
我希望我能
I hope I'm a waitress at the Cheesecake Factory
做一辈子奶酪店的服务员
for my whole life.
这是讽刺么?
Was that sarcasm?
不
No.
那这句呢?
Was that sarcasm?
是
Yes.
-那这句  -闭嘴吧
Was that sar-- Stop it!
佩妮  这有个你的包裹
Penny, you appear to have a package here.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
肯定是我订的贝雷帽
This must be the beret I ordered.
都是几个月前的事了  是以前订的
A couple of months ago. It was back-ordered.
你知道么  贝雷帽
Did you know the beret is an example
是女性时尚参考男性军服
of a piece of women's fashion
很好的例子
adapted from male military uniforms?
另一个迷人的例子是肩饰
Another fascinating example is the epaulet.
他没说谎
He's not lying.
他真的很喜欢肩饰
He does find that fascinating.
无所谓了
Okay, whatever.
我并没有为了一个贝雷帽
It's not like I'm running up and down the streets
在街上逛来逛去
just buying myself berets.
我订了一个  一个月前
I bought one, like, a month ago,
那是之前订的
and it was back-ordered.
-现在终于寄到了  有问题么？  -没有
Look, it finally arrived, all right? All right.
我的天  你能不能别那么多事
Oh, my God, would you just get off my case?!
真奇怪
Weird.
太好了  原来这不是正常的对话模式
Oh, good, that was an unusual interaction.
我本来还不确定
I wasn't sure.
你们之前吵过架?
Did you guys have an argument?
没啊
No.
你肯定干什么事惹着她来着
Well, you clearly did something to aggravate her.
我没概念了
I'm at a loss.
高兴地话  你可以去查查我的社交日志
If you like, you can review my daily log of social interactions
看看有没有我没注意到的失误
and see if there's a blunder I overlooked.
你的这份
Here you go.
对  你还多欠我两块
Oh, you owe me another two dollars.
木须肉涨价了
The price of moo shu pork went up.
当个"可恶的犹太人"真是越来越难了
It's getting tougher and tougher to be a bad Jew.
佩妮  你的龙虾酱炒虾
Here you go, Penny. Shrimp with lobster sauce.
谢谢  莱纳德  我该给多少
Thank you, Leonard. What's my share?
没事  我请你
Don't worry about it. It's my treat.
不  多少钱?
No, really, how much?
差不多10块11块吧
It's... whatever. $10, $11.
到底是10块还是11块?
Well, which is it, $10 or $11?
14块5  真没多少
$14.50. But it's no biggie.
下次你请就好了
You'll get the next one.
又怎么了
What?
他在猜如果
He was just wondering if he wore
他穿紧身上衣和牛仔裤的话
skintight jeans and a tank top
是不是也能免费吃到鲜虾捞面了
if he'd get his shrimp lo mein for free.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我用我的身体来让别人请客?
That I'm using my body to get dinner?
我是骗中餐小姐
That I'm some kind of Chinese food prostitute?
对  拉杰  你什么意思
Yeah, Raj, what are you saying?
告诉你吧  哥们
'Cause let me tell you something, buddy.
我靠自己的钱过活  明白?
I pay my own way in this world, okay?
我不需要靠别人
I don't rely on anybody!
这又怎么了?
What was that about?
当他感受到压力的时候就尿急
He has a nervous bladder when he's stressed out.
像小狗似的
Kind of like a puppy.
莱纳德  拿着  10, 11, 12... 14块
Here, Leonard-- $10, $11, $12... $14.
是14块5  算了
It was $14.50, but it's okay.
太好了  饭(双关:正餐)来了
Oh, good. Dinner's here.
没错  正餐来了
Yes, dinner's here, and I'm having some.
而我只能吃外卖
I'm having takeout food.
-好吧  -说得太他妈对了
Okay. You're damn right it's okay.
我在饭店吃了四天的残羹剩饭
I've been having leftovers at the restaurant for like four days,
今天我想换个花样  去告我啊
and I wanted something different. So sue me.
请原谅  佩妮
Forgive me, Penny, but that would be
那是诉讼挑唆的意思
the very definition of a frivolous lawsuit.
谢尔顿  我有了钱马上还你
Sheldon, look, I will pay you back as soon as I can.
只是要宽限我几天
You just have to give me more time.
等等  你借她钱来着
Oh, wait, you lent her money?
她需要钱
She needed money.
你看上去很有压力
You seem under pressure.
我借给你的够么
Did I not lend you a sufficient amount?
你可以再来点
Because I can give you more.
你很喜欢这样不是么
Oh, you know, you would just love that, wouldn't you?
打开你的小蛇把守的罐子
Yeah. You would just love to open up your little snake can
然后把钱施舍给那些付不了帐单的姑娘
and throw some money at the girl who can't pay her bills.
你去哪
Where are you going?
回家 在那我不用像个犯人似的被审问
Going home, where I won't be interrogated like a criminal.
我忘了幸运饼干了
I forgot my fortune cookie.
以防你们谁有贼心
In case either of you have larceny in your heart,
提醒一下  我已经把钱从小蛇罐子挪走了
you should know that I've moved my money out of the snake can.
但如果真缺钱的话
But if you're ever short,
在绿灯侠的屁股里总能找到50块
there's always a couple of 50s in Green Lantern's ass.
温馨的烛光哈
A little mood lighting, huh?
因为没付帐单
When I didn't pay my bill,
水电局认为
the Department of Water and Power thought
我会享受这样的气氛
I would enjoy the ambience.
这样看来他们还挺周到的
Yeah, they're very considerate that way.
我用谢尔顿的钱付了房租
I used Sheldon's money to pay my rent.
然后只剩14块
Then I had like $14 left over.
14块?
$14, huh?
放回你的口袋里
Put it back in your pocket,
要不然我会找个其他的地方搁
or I'll find some other place to put it.
已经放回去了
Back in the pocket it goes.
要知道  谢尔顿真不在乎 什么时候你还他钱
Look, you do understand that Sheldon really doesn't care when he gets the money back.
事实上 正是像这种为数不多的特点
It's actually one of the few idiosyncrasies that doesn't make you want to,
才让你对他没有杀意
you know, kill him.
但这并不是最大的问题所在
Yeah, well, that's not really my big problem.
你不就欠了点费吗
So you're a little behind on your bills.
谁不欠费啊
Everybody gets behind on their bills.
我知道  但这和我的预期差别太大了
Yeah, I know, it's just... this wasn't the plan.
我没打算变成现在这样的
It wasn't supposed to go this way.
那你原来打算怎么样
Well, what was the plan?
当六个月服务员然后成为电影明星
Um, waitress for six months and then become a movie star.
有没有B计划?
Was there a plan B?
电视明星
TV star.
可能没你想的那么糟
It's probably not as bad as you think.
让我们看看
Let's take a look.
说不定能找到些能缩减的开支
Maybe we can find some corners to cut.
这有一些
Oh, here's something.
如果你家没有电
If you don't have electricity,
那你可能也不需要有线网络了
then you probably don't need cable.
只是说说而已
Just a suggestion.
价值170美金的表演课程?
$170 dollars for acting classes?
不  我不能放弃我的表演课
Oh, no, I can't give up my acting classes.
我是个专业女演员
I'm a professional actress.
你有能赚钱的表演工作?
You've had an acting job where you got paid?
这不是评判"专业"的标准
That is not the definition of professional.
实际上这就是...我们还是继续看吧
Actually, it kind of... Let's keep looking.
哪儿来的洛杉矶高等法院的1800美金罚款?
Whoa, what's $1,800 to the Los Angeles County Superior Court?
没什么
Oh, that's nothing.
没什么?
Nothing?
貌似你以4000英里的时速
It sounds like you got caught speeding
超速驾驶被逮着了
going 4,000 miles an hour.
还记得科特吗
Well, remember Kurt?
你那个前男友?
Your ex-boyfriend?
嗯
Yeah.
他在警车上小便被抓了
He got arrested for taking a whiz on a cop car.
-什么?  -他喝醉了
-What? -He was drunk.
但愿如此
I would hope so.
话说他有很多罚款单
Anyway, he had a bunch of outstanding tickets
还有一堆告票
and a bench warrant,
所以  我帮他付了罚款
so I, you know, I paid his fines.
他把钱还给你了吗
Did he pay you back?
没有  不过他会还的
No, but he will.
这还建立在他是个天生没信用 经常喝醉
And that's based on the inherent credit-worthiness of people
还在警车里小便的人渣的基础之上的?
who get drunk and urinate on police vehicles?
莱纳德  我不会打电话给科特向他讨债的
Leonard, I'm not gonna call up Kurt and ask him for money.
那...
Well...
你准备怎么做?
what are you gonna do?
我也不知道
I don't know,
不过我可能得去找个便宜点的地方住了
but I may have to find a cheaper place to live.
不...
Oh, no...
你不会想这样做的
Oh, you don't want to do that.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
搬家要花很多钱的
Moving is a big deal.
你得去超市买那些置物箱
You have to go to the supermarket and get boxes,
那些箱子不干净的话  你的书就会有股甜瓜味
and if they're not clean, then your books smell like melons,
就像...
and it's just, like...
你干吗不找个室友搬进来住呢
Why don't you just get a roommate and stay here
你认识什么适合的人不
do you know anybody
我肯定那个跟谢尔顿一起住的人
Well, I'm sure the guy living with Sheldon
决不会介意搬来跟你住的
wouldn't mind moving in with you.
莱纳德  亲爱的  如果我们开始一起住的话
Oh, Leonard, honey, if we started living together,
我会一直都缠着你的
I wouldn't be able to keep my hands off you.
真的吗
Really?
你以为我表演课是白上的吗
And you thought my acting lessons were a waste of money.
那些木须肉在我的十二指肠里烧穿了个洞
This moo shu pork's burning a hole through my duodenum.
利未记(圣经)第十一章第三节里说
Leviticus 11:3:
"凡蹄分两瓣  倒嚼的走兽
"Only that which parteth the hoof and cheweth the cud
你们都可以吃"
among the beasts shall ye eat."
你每次吃汉堡王的天椒皇堡的时候
Hey, do I mock you with the Bhagavad-Gita every time
我有拿印度圣歌来取笑你吗
you scarf down a Whopper?
你们在干嘛
Hey, what's going on?
我们在玩火之谷冒险游戏 目标是拿到至尊王冠
We're on a quest through the Valley of Fire to acquire the sacred crown.
你想要火之谷吗 这里就有
You want the Valley of Fire? It's right here.
你们想不想玩真人冒险游戏?
Hey, you guys want to go on a real live quest?
出去玩?  我刚弄了杯可可
Outside? I just made cocoa.
来吧  会很好玩的
Come on. It'll be fun.
到底是什么游戏?
What is it?
你们还记得 佩妮的前男友科特吗
Do you guys remember penny's ex-boyfriend Kurt?
对  就是他
Yeah, that's him.
原来他欠了佩妮很多钱 我想去问他讨回来
It turns out he owes Penny a lot of money, and I'm gonna go get it from him.
谁想参加
Who's with me?
两个六
Ooh, double sixes.
你们真的忍心让我一个人去吗
Really? You're just gonna let me go by myself?
太棒了  我得到了一把剑
Oh, cool, I got a sword.
我可能需要点帮助
I could use some help.
给你
Here.
真难以置信
xyzzz xyzzz You guys are unbelievable.
你们玩游戏就是为了模拟冒险场景
You play a game to simulate adventure,
但真的可以出去冒险的时候 你们就都窝囊了
but when there's real adventure out there in the real world, you just wimp out.
莱纳德  还记得我们上次去找这个男人
Leonard, do you not recall the last time we visited this gentleman,
结果回来的时候裤子都没了吗
we returned home without pants?
我记得
I do.
你确定么  但你提议表明你已经忘记了
Are you sure? Because your proposal suggests that you don't.
我不怕他
I'm not afraid of him.
好吧  莱纳德刚才清楚地表明了他的问题
All right. Leonard fairly calls the question:
谁愿意放弃我们的游戏而去面对
Who is in favor of abandoning our game and confronting
佩妮那个类固醇激素旺盛的前男友
Penny's steroid-infused ex-boyfriend
并以一种自杀的方式去向他要钱
in a suicidal mission to extract money from him?
代我们向科特问好
Say hi to Kurt for us.
你们说  佛罗多离开夏尔 把魔戒带去莫都的时候
Excuse me. When Frodo left the Shire to take the one ring to Mordor,
山姆怀斯  皮平和梅利有没有陪他一起去?
didn't Samwise, Pippin and Merry go with him?
-他们去了  -所以
-They did. -Well?
他们那时很艰难  莱纳德
They had a terrible time of it, Leonard.
再说  没有人剥了他们的裤子
Plus, no one stole their pants.
好吧  好好享受你们的游戏
Fine. Enjoy your little game.
我自己去完成这个冒险
I'll make this quest on my own.
莱纳德  等等
Leonard, wait.
带件外套去
Take a jacket.
外面有点凉飕飕的
It's shpritzing a little.
你们都是损友
You guys suck.
去吧  求你们了  他太健壮了
Come on, please? He's so big.
大家都清楚我们的计划了
Okay, is everyone clear on the plan?
嗯  库萨帕里准备要尿裤子了
Yes. Koothrappali's going to wet himself,
我准备要吐了  谢尔顿准备逃跑了
I'm gonna throw up, Sheldon's gonna run away,
你准备要死了
and you're going to die.
我们对一下表吧
Shall we synchronize our watches?
伙计们  我们有四个人 他只有一个人
Guys, there are four of us and one of him.
也就是说他将有更多的战利品
Which means his triumph will be even larger.
吟游诗人会为他写歌
Minstrels will write songs about him.
这样吧
Okay, how about this?
我来跟他谈
I'll do the talking.
你们就站在我后面假装很凶悍
You just stand behind me and try to look formidable.
出门前应该上个厕所的
I should've peed before we left.
什么事
Yeah?
你好  科特
Hi, Kurt.
你是莱尼吗
Lenny, right?
其实我不喜欢被叫莱尼  不过没关系
I don't really go by Lenny, but that's okay.
你还记得
Um, you remember
谢尔顿  霍华德 和拉杰吗
Sheldon, Howard and Raj.
不记得  你想干嘛
No. What do you want?
他不记得我了
He don't remember me?
他怎能不记得我了
How could he not remember me?
谢尔顿  别这样
Sheldon, not now.
我可记得他
I remember him.
事情是这样的  佩妮的经济出现了状况
Okay, here it is. Penny's in kind of a financial jam,
而你欠她的钱  对于缓解危机
and the money that you owe her would go a long way
相当有帮助
to solving her problems.
于是她叫你来拿钱
And she sent you to get it from me?
当然不  她是不好意思来取
No, no, she's too proud to ask for the money.
此外  我认为欠债还钱  天经地义
I, on the other hand, feel you should honor your debt.
你认为
You do?
说"认为"  语气已经较强烈了
"Feel" is a kind of a... it's a strong word.
我希望对你来说  这词儿还算是礼貌用语
Um, I just think it would be a nice gesture on your part.
我想什么时候还就什么时候还
She'll get it when she gets it.
你看  问题解决了
Well, there you go. Problem solved.
目的达到了
A successful quest.
我们快去找个有干净厕所的加油站吧
Now let's go find a gas station with a clean bathroom.
不  问题还没解决
No, the problem isn't solved.
他根本没理会我们
He just blew us off.
我明白了
I've got it.
因为上次见面时  我正穿着万圣节服饰
He didn't remember me because the last time we met,
所以他没记得我
I was in a Halloween costume.
拜托  莱纳德  我们走吧
Come on, Leonard, let's go.
不  你们想走就走吧
No. You can leave if you want to.
我必须有始有终
I'm gonna see this through.
那好吧
Okay.
其实本来就不该带你们来
I guess, technically, that was my fault.
拿不到佩妮的钱  我是不会走的
I'm not leaving here without Penny's money.
你的后援团去哪了
What happened to your backup?
我可不需要后援团
I don't need backup.
因为正义站在我这边
I have right on my side.
而且我长裤里还多穿了条平脚裤
And I'm wearing cargo shorts under my pants.
恭喜你
congratulations.
你没有拿到现金
You may not have succeeded in getting cash,
却打到了正式的欠条
but you did secure a formal acknowledgment of the debt.
或许我们应该把你头拿去公证一下
Maybe we should have your head notarized.
不介意的话  我还是想尿尿
If anybody cares, I still have to pee
-谢尔顿在吗  -在的  等等
-Hey. Is Sheldon here? -Yeah. Hang on.
谢尔顿
Sheldon!
帽子不错
Nice hat.
最近流行这款
It's kind of a fashionable look these days.
看起来像捕鱼的
Maybe if you're working on a tuna boat.
佩妮  你来啦
Hello, Penny.
谢尔顿  这是你的钱
Sheldon, here is your money.
非常感谢  帮了大忙了
Thank you very much. It helped a lot.
讽刺吗
Sarcasm?
不
No.
该死  我还是没有摸透其中奥秘
Darn. I can't seem to get the hang of that.
虽然这与我无关
Hey, I know it's none of my business,
但这些钱你从哪来的
but where did the money come from?
就如你说的  我省下一部分开支
Well, I cut back my expenses like you said
在餐厅里多加几小时的班
and picked up a few more hours at the restaurant,
但最主要的是  突然间
but the biggest thing was, out of the blue,
科特回来了
Kurt shows up
还把他欠我的钱还给了我
and gives me the money he owes me..
真的吗  他有说为什么吗
Really? Did he say why?
是的  他说他觉得很惭愧
Yes, he said he was feeling guilty
还钱本是天经地义
and wanted to do what was right.
就这样
That's it?
他没有对其突然良心发现 给出任何理由吗
Did he give any reason as to why he came to this moral epiphany?
没有  我认为他真的改变了
Nope. I just think he's really changed.
我们明晚要共进晚餐
We're having dinner tomorrow night,
有机会戴新买的贝雷帽了
and I get to wear my new beret.
再见
Bye, guys.
拜拜
Bye.
为你骄傲  莱纳德
Well done, Leonard.
幕后英雄从不邀功
The true hero doesn't seek adulation.
他为了正义和公道而斗争
He fights for right and justice simply
完全是天性使然
because it's his nature.
佩妮和她的垃圾前男友又好上了
Penny's hooking up with her jerk of an ex-boyfriend,
而我的前额却还有擦不掉的墨迹
and I have indelible ink on my forehead!
这可是荣誉徽章
That's your badge of honor
你也可以称其为  战斗的印记
your warrior's wound, if you will.
我错了
I was wrong.
吟游诗人会为你写首歌的
Minstrels will write songs about you.
真棒
Great.
*有个勇敢的青年叫莱纳德*
* There once was a brave lad named Leonard *
*背着一个悦耳的小提琴*
* With a fi-fi fiddle dee-dee *
*面对凶恶的怪兽时*
* He faced a fearsome giant *
*正巧拉杰想要尿尿*
* While Raj just wanted to pee. *